Yushan Wang

8730 Costa Verde Blvd,2425 Costa Verde Village, yuw688@ucsd.edu, 6097513319

EDUCATION

University of California San Diego, California

Sept. 2017 – June. 2021

B.S. in Computer Engineering

GPA:3.82

B.S. in Applied Mathematics (Completed)

GPA:3.92

Honors/Awards: Provost Honor (2016-2020)

• Relevant Courses: Neural Networks and Deep Learning, Supervised Machine Learning Algorithms

Data structure and Algorithms, Numerical Analysis, computational statistics

• Engineering Analysis & Statistics, Engineering Probability and Statistics

Math complex and real analysis, data sampling

SUMMARY

Current Junior at University of California San Diego dedicated to computer engineering and applied mathematics. A good team player and experienced problem-solving student with detail-oriented mindset seeking tech-related internship opportunities Always keen to embrace new ideas and knowledge.

• Programming Skills: Java

4 years

Python, MATLAB, R

2 years

JavaScript

1 year

• Software Skills: Linux, Git, PyCharm, VSCode

IntelliJ, Adobe Premiere, Ableton, SolidWorks, ANSYS, OrCAD

• Certification: GRE 331/340

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Teaching assistant in Math Department

Teaching Assistant 09.2019 - present

Being the teaching assistant in the math department of UCSD, and tutoring Math10B in the Fall quarter 2019, and Math 20C in Winter quarter 2020.

EXPERIENCE AND PROJECTS

COVID-19 Face Mask Detector by TensorFlow and OpenCV

May 2020 - Jun 2020

Using Caffe-DNN for face detection technology

And VGG-16 for the training on mask/no_mask classifier

Link: https://github.com/YushanWang9801/COGS181/blob/master/Cogs_181_Final_Project.pdf

Video Game Classification by Machine Learning Methods

Oct 2019 - Dec 2019

Using data contains 170000 strategy games on the Apple App Store from Kaggle.

Segmented products by principal component analysis and k-means, mean shift clustering in python Forecast user ratings of each cluster game using time series analysis

"When to meet" web-application design

Sep 2019 - Jan 2020

A webpage application design using firebase as database allowing users to collect time and location preferences from all members of the meeting

Using JavaScript to complete the entire UI and webpage programming

Speech to Text Diagnosis Records

May2018 - Jun 2018

The project composed at HLTH Hackathon Las Vegas, June 2018.

Using API transform speech to text and extract medical terms to form medical diagnosis.

OTHER CONTACT

- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/yushan-wang-270a031aa/
- GitHub: https://github.com/YushanWang9801